A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. Restoration of Rights Files, 1996-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 47.60 cu. ft. (Box 138-274)
  - Subseries B: Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006.
    - 15 January 2005 to 14 January 2006 (Accession 42513)
      - Candelaria, Donzella Missouri, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Canty, Milton Joe, granted 13 July 2005 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Carico, Douglas Clay, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Carlisle, Allan Drew, granted 22 August 2005 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Carlson, Eric Leonard, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carlton, James Edward, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carmalt, James D., granted 24 October 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carnes, Stephen D., Jr., granted 22 November 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carrico, Lois Ann, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carrier, Steven Michael, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carson, Shontel D., granted 1 July 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carter, Bernard, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Carter, Clifford Llewenlyn, Jr., granted 1 June 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Ella Mae, granted 16 May 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Joseph Samuel, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Lisa Annette, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Michael Keith, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Regina Ann, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Walter James, Sr., granted 17 November 2005 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Walter James, Sr., granted 17 November 2005 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Carwile, Kathy, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Cary, Allison Juanita, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Cary, Darryl Wayne, Sr., granted 27 October 2005 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Cason, Harold, Jr., granted 24 March 2005 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Cason, Stanley Andrew, granted 13 July 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Cassell (Mitchell), Wendy Elaine, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Catchot, Kimberly Grace, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Catron, Leonard W., granted 1 March 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Cauthorne, Keith Alan, granted 22 August 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Chaffin, Laura Davidson, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Chambers (Hall), Olivia, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Chambliss, Matthew P., Jr., granted 7 November 2005 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Chamlee, Robert Webster, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Chandler, McKinley Scott, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Chapman, Brian Richard, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Chatlin, Robert Lee, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Cheely, Brenda M., granted 11 May 2005 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Childress, Lisa Lewis, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Chitwood, Giles B., granted 10 June 2005 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Christian, Jacob Lewis, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Christian, Melody, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Christian, Ronald E., granted 18 August 2005 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Christian, Stacey Leon, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Christmas, James Gordon, III, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Church, Velvet Ann, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Clark, Gerry Wesley, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Clark, Linda, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Clay, Charlotte Marie, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Clay, Mark, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Cline, Donald Harrison, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Clyne, Ralph Herman, granted 25 July 2005 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Coates, Annette, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Coates, Rodney Oldham, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Cobb, Celeste Stephens, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Cobbs, Kenneth, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Cockerille, Brenda Finnell, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Cohen, David Alan, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Colby, David Brian, granted 15 June 2005 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Cole, Brenda Susan, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Cole, Frederick Bernard, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Coleman, Crystal Lynn, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Coleman, James L., granted 21 November 2005 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Coleman, Saint Matthew, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Coleman, Thomas Henry, granted 5 January 2006 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Colley, Anne Louise, granted 15 November 2005 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Collins, Almer Lee, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Collins, Cristy H., granted 24 October 2005 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Collins, Paul L., Jr., granted 26 August 2005 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Comer, Dennis Ardel, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Compher, James S., granted 3 October 2005 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Compton, Phillip, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Conner, Kaviet Anthony, Sr., granted 25 July 2005 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - Conner, Larry Wayne, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - Conrow, David Michael, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - Consolvo, Andrew Benjamin, IV, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - Cook, Tommy Gene, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - Cooper, John James, granted 5 January 2006 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Cooper, Tonya Leona, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Cooper, Willie Antonio, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Cooper-Mickey, Lenora Denise, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Copeland, Debra Denise, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Copeland, Karen, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Correll, Jamie Elisha, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Corvin, Matthew David, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Cosby, Jerome Everett, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Cosby, Robert Thomas, Jr., granted 1 June 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Cottle, Susan Gail Collins, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Coulter, Ruth Marlene, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Coulter, Samantha L., granted 24 October 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Cousins, Maurice D., Sr., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Cox, Fred Huston, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Creager, Billy R., granted 21 September 2005 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Crespin, Gail R., granted 3 January 2006 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Crimmins, Patrick John, Jr., granted 6 December 2005 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Crisafi, Salvatore J., granted 7 November 2005 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Cropp, Leroy Sylvester, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Cross, Tamara LaCraie, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Crossen, Warren Eric, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Crossman, Angela W., granted 9 December 2005 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Cruz, Allen Dale Fabian, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Cullison, Alexander C., granted 1 August 2005 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Culp, Tyra Michelle, granted 223 February 2005 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Cunningham, Paul Risteen, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Curney, Eleanor Bernadine, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Curtin, Robert E., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Cusati, Anthony, III, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Cyrus, Matthew Mahone, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Dabney, Craig S., granted 9 September 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Dabney, Vincent Garfield, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Dale, Mark Franklin, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Damico, James G., granted 14 September 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Dandridge, Shawn LaMont, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Daniel, Reginald Lamont, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Daniels, Doris Anne, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Daniels, Gloria Dean, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Daniels, Levi E., granted 3 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Darby, Carolyn, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Darrow, Cary Alan, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Daugherty, Stephen Walter, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Davis, Bryan Keith, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Davis, Calvin Ray, Jr., granted 3 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Carl Augusta, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Kenneth Elwood, Jr., granted 7 November 2005 (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Michael, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Samuel, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Trena Renae, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Tyrone Deshon, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Day, Pamela Jean, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Day, Richard Ernest, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - DeBruhl, Adele Rossi, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Deel, James Melvin, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - DeFord, Roy Samuel, Sr., granted 7 November 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - DeHart, Danny L., granted 14 September 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Deloach, Roger Lee, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - De Los Rios, Alessia Michele, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - Delp, Kevin Hobart, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - Demery, Thomas T., granted 24 October 2005 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - Dendy, Terrance Kywan, granted 21 September 2005 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - DeVergie, Brenda F., granted 24 January 2005 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - Dew, Charles Roderick, granted 11 July 2005 (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - Dice, Larry Moffett, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dickens, Clara Wanda, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dickens, John Vernon "Shonn", granted 26 August 2005 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dickerson, Darlene Ann, granted 23 February 2005 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dickerson, Madison Clarence, Jr., granted 14 November 2005 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dillard, Dana Roy, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dillard, Deborah Marie, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - Dillon, Matthew Wade, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - Dixon, Leo, granted 21 January 2005 (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - Dixon, Ted Lawrence, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - Doane, Larry Wayne, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - Dodd, Sharon Kay, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Doddridge, James, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Dooley, James Neal, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Dooley, Richard Lee, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Doolittle, James Eugene, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Dorsey, Robert Lake, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Douffas, Judith Ann, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Dowdy, Kenneth Wayne, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Dozier, Douglas Jabbar, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Drew, Shirley Marie, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Duffey, Wanda Bryant, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Dunbar, Joseph Wade, Sr., granted 4 October 2005 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - DuVall, Joseph W., granted 6 July 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Dyson, David Rodney, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Eades, Tanja Surita, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - East, Dan Truman, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Easton, Mark Allen, Sr., granted 9 December 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Eaton, Colt Forrest, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Eckstone-Hayes, Christine, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Edelman, Sally Ann, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Edwards, Andrew Chandler, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Edwards, Ronald Lee, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Eichman, Peter, granted 7 May 2005 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Elam, Rodney Darryl, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Eldridge, Timothy B., granted 29 March 2005 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Elliott, Lisa P., granted 17 August 2005 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Elliotte, Cassandra Yvette, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Ellison, Marian J., granted 16 November 2005 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Epperly, James Franklin, Jr., granted 18 August 2005 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Epps, Jacqueline Denise, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Epps, John Henry, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Esho, Sampson Lewis, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Ethridge, Susan H., granted 4 October 2005 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Evans, Donell, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Evans, John Wayne, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Evans-Brown, Susan G., granted 26 August 2005 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Everett, Patricia Louise, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Everton, David Wayne, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Evins, Garry Anthony, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Ewell, Brian Miles, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Ewing, Corey D., granted 17 May 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Fagnani, Lori-Ann, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Fain, Michael LaDon, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Fain, Shauna Lynn, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Faison, Raymond Lamont, III, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Farley, Tania A., granted 10 June 2005 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Ferguson, Anita Cox, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Ferneyhough, Barbara Alice, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Ferrell, Anthony Scott, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Field, Maurice F., granted 19 August 2005 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Fike, Terry Lee, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Fincham, Debra Susan, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Finney, Elena Jane, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Fisher, Van Ray, granted 26 September 2005 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Flanary, Robert Guy, III, granted 15 November 2005 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Fleet, Dennis Michael, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Fletcher, Jean R., granted 14 September 2005 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Flint, Richard Austin, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Flores, Rosa G., granted 4 October 2005 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Flynn, Larry Wayne, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Foley, Deborah Kay, granted 28 November 2005 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Fortner, Kenner Delano, Jr., granted 1 March 2005 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Foster, Amonica Pope, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Foutz, Charles Edward, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Foxx, Sara Michelle, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Franklin, Judy Harmon, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Franz, Keith Lee, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Frazier, Stanley A., granted 1 July 2005 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - French, Chad Derrick, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Fridley, Vernon L., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Frost, Robin, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Frye, Steven, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Frye, Wayne A., granted 1 March 2005 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Futrell, Vanessa Joyce, granted 31 March 2005 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Gaffney, Michael A., granted 14 November 2005 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Gaines, Donald, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Gaines-Canady, Kimberlyn, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Gamble, Philip Cooper, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Garand, Edgar Wernor, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Garland, Roland Claudie, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Garnett, Selden Hunter, III, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Garrett, Gloria Jean, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Garrett, Johnny Glenn, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Garrett, Joseph L., granted 1 August 2005 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Gates, Larry Dean, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Gauldin, Gerald Lee, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Gears, Lesley Marie, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Geis, Wanita R., granted 4 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - George, George Andrew, Jr., granted 24 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - German, Eloise, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Gibson, Allen Sylvester, Jr., granted 11 May 2005 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Gibson, John Shannon, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Gibson, Lilly Mae, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Gibson, Michael, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Gibson, Patricia T., granted 6 December 2005 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Gilchrist, Joseph A., granted 2 May 2005 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Giles, Alicia LaNell, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Gill, George, Jr., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Gilleece, Terri Lynn, granted 21 September 2005 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Gills, Howard Jason, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Gillespie, James G., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Gilreath, Brian Douglas, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Gilreath, Kimberley Sharman, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Glass, Jimmy Lee, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Gleim, Arthur F., granted 21 November 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Gluth, Richard Edwin, Jr., granted 26 August 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Goad, Shawn Patrick, granted 23 February 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Godley, Lalita Michele, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Goldman, Cynthia Delores, granted 23 February 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Goode, Renia Patsy Comer, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Goode, William H., Sr., granted 23 February 2005 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Goodman, Sherman Lee, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Goodson, Tyreese LaRue, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Gordon, Clarence Lee, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Gouterman, Steven M., granted 26 August 2005 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Gower, William Terry, granted 28 November 2005 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Graham, Donald Greg, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Graham, Ernest Lee, Jr., granted 29 March 2005 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Granby, Kenneth M., granted 1 November 2005 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Gravely, Lenora Mae, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Graves-Lynn, Shelly, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Gravley, Marie Moses, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Gray, James Edward, Sr., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Gray, Leonard A., granted 1 June 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Gray, Michelynne Devalle, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Green, Demetria F., granted 14 September 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Green, LaTeasha R., granted 10 June 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Green, Sabrina Marie, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Green, Wanda Lorraine, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Greene, Bernard, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Greene, Frances Inell, granted 12 July 2005 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Greene, Imelda Hall, granted 14 November 2005 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Greene, MacArthur, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Greene, Timothy Vernon, Jr., granted 6 December 2005 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Greer, Donald Wade, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Gregory, Carl Edward, granted 12 July 2005 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Gregory, Sherry Leigh, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Gregory, Stacey Lynn, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Griffin, Emmett Lloyd, Sr., granted 14 September 2005 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Griffin, Josephine Belcher, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Griffin, Robin Louise, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Griffiths, Ashley W., granted 3 January 2006 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Grimm, Jason Matthew, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Grimm, Stephen W., granted 18 October 2005 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Gromkoski, William Joseph, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Guild, Barbara Ann, granted 3 October 2005 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Gupton, Rose Marie, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Guyer, Greg S., granted 1 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Hackley, Francesca Demitrius, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Haden, John Patterson, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Hagood, Kenny, granted 29 March 2005 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Hagwood, Stewart Lee, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Hairston, Aphrodite Tinoka, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Hairston, Clyde Antonia, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Hairston, Nathaniel, Sr., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Hajacos, James Preston, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Hall, David Leroy, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Hall, Harry Gadsby, III, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Hall, James Michael, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Hall, Jerry Edward, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Hall, Jon Walter, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Halloran, Charles Stuart, granted 28 November 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hamberry, Ellis Corinthian, granted 18 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hamel, Hank Mollie, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hamilton, Larry Joe, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hamilton, Thomas Marshall, granted 11 May 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hamm, Christopher Eugene, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hammersley, Shannon Marie, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Hammond, Penny Lynn, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Hammond, Samuel Luke, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Hampton, Joyce, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Hancock, David Lee, II, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Hankins, Kenneth Wayne, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 241, Folder 1)